You want these people.
They order your products, sign up for
your services, enroll in your classes,
read your opinions,
and watch your videos.
You'll never see them,
but they know you.
Through your website.
Or
maybe not.
Your website's visitors aren't
a faceless mass of identical mouse
clickers, but a vibrant community of
individuals with varying tastes, styles,
and abilities.
This includes people with disabilities.
It's important for web designers and
developers to realize that what they see
currently on their computer, at their
resolution, with their browser and their
operating system, is not going
to be necessarily the same thing that
everybody else sees.